MD. Shahriar Kabir

Front-end Web Developer specialized in React





& ABOUT ME

I'm Shahriar Kabir, A 27 years old Self Taught Front-end web developer with over Two years of professional experience, specialized in React.is. I am looking for an opportunity where I can grow my skills and become a full-stack developer.



EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer

Tappware Solutions LTD, Dhaka / Sep 2019 - Jan 2021

Responsibility

- e-Filing system (nothi.gov.bd). My job was to update their previous PHP website to a react web app. As a junior developer, I mostly work on creating reusable components.
- Rest API Integration Using Redux-Saga
- Creating reusable Components Using Ant-design UI library

Front-End Developer

Createdevs / Apr 2021 - Dec 2021

Responsibility

- Creating Admin Panel For Dhaka-eats(dhaka-eats.com).
- Connect Node JS Backend API on Next JS application.
- Server State and Cache Management Using React-guery.
- Figma to JSX using Tailwind CSS
- API integration on React-native Aplication
- Using Magnus UI for Building React-native App

Freelance Projects

- 1. Frontend Developer (Contract) https://anwartraders.com.bd --- A Next JS E-commerce site. This UI is from Theme forest popular theme called Martfury.
- 2. Frontend Developer (Contract) https://www.myfarmbd.com/ Its an Financial website for Farmer of Bangladesh.
- 3. Wordpress Headless Blog with Next JS https://react-wp-export- japan.vercel.app/



Email:

toshahriarshakil@gmail.com

Phone:

+8801780503417

Address:

Dhaka, Bangladesh

LinkedIn:

Shahriar-Shakil

Github:

Shahriar-Shakil

Upwork:

Shahriar kabir



SKILLS

Iavascript Typescript Node IS React Next JS Redux Recoil **SWR React-Query** WP Headless CMS Ant-Design Material-UI Tailwind-CSS Styled Component **Bootstrap** SSR **API** Integration Server State & Caching React-native



EDUCATION

BBA at IUBAT years 2015-2018 (dropout)